

Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

PROFILE

Gender: Male Nationality: Iranian Birth Date: 8/25/1983

A software engineer with more than 10 years experience in software developing with Several roles including developer, designer, team lead in various projects.

Communicative, high interaction with team-mates, responsibility and perseverance, and issue solving. Motivated and intrested in learning new concepts, technical challanges and distributed systems and also improving the Software Quality(functional or non-functional)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science from Sheikh Bahaee Isfahan University in Software Engineering from September 2000 to September 2006.

LANGUAGES

English

Persian

CONTACT

Email: arm.khani@gmail.com Mobile: +98 912 8589 456

LinkedIn: Arman Ajabkhani's profile

Address: No. 23, Parastoo2 Alley, Kaj St.,

Taherkhani St., Tehran, Iran

WORK EXPERIENCE

SNAPP(Largest smart transportation system in Iran)

Senior Java Developer

July 2019 - Present

Senior java developer in Fintech team:

- Designing and implementing new generation Financial management services for users and drivers.
- Providing services for more than 2 million users.
- Developing services with SpringBoot, Spring Cloud, MySql, OpenShift and Redis.
- Responsible for designing and development of Payment and Wallet Management Services.

Sava Arman Kish(a crypto-currencies Exchange start-up)

Senior Java Developer

Nov 2018 - Jul 2019

Senior java developer in the Exchange back-end team:

- Developing reactive services using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- Responsible for designing, development and maintaining CRM and notification services.
- Designing and implementing features and fixing bug in several micro-services.

TOSAN(Payment and Banking solution provider)

Senior Java Developer /Team Lead

Nov 2011 -Nov 2018

Team lead in Channel Manager team:

- Mentoring, coaching, training and planning tasks for the team members.
- Analysis, Design, Development, Deployment & Maintenance several applications & micro-services.
- Designing and developing some complicated features in open banking API.

Senior java developer in Channel Manager Team:

- Developing functionalities for tracking and authentication and authorization.
- Developing and maintaining Exchange and Corporate Banking subsystems.
- Providing serveral financial and payment services for front-end teams.
- Developing and implementing RMI and Web Services (REST / SOAP JAX-WS).
- Implementing many feature in Persistence layer using JPA/Hibernate

Elm o Sanat

C#/ASP.NET Developer

Sep 2010 -Oct 2011

- Implementing several new features and maintain in the School product.
- Implementing features in a custom report generator.
- Implementing virtual replication on SQL Server with use web service.

Netbina (Online advertising solution provider)

Junior C#/ASP.NET Developer

Oct 2006 -Mar 2009

- Implementing several functionalities for the advertising products.
- Developing a several feature in Blog Service with C# and ASP.NET.



Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Java / JVM	Spring
SOA/Micro-services	Spring Boot
Test Driven Development	Spring MVC
Event Driven Architecture	Spring Security
Software Architecture Patterns	Spring Cloud
Design Patterns	Spring Batch
Live Migration	Spring Data / JPA/ Hibernate
Concurrent Programming	Spring AOP / aspectj
Reactive Programming	Vert.x / RxJava
RESTful Web Services	Redis / Redisson
SOAP / JAX-WS /JAX-RS	Oracle
Docker	MySQL / SQL Server
OpenShift	Gradle / Maven
Jenkins/Gitlab CI/CD	Swagger UI/ Codegen
Financial / Banking / Payment Systems	Git / Subversion / TFS
Crypto Currency Exchanges	ActiveMQ/ Rabbit MQ
UML / Agile and RUP Methodologies	Apache Tomcat
Confluence / SharePoint / Documenting	OAuth / JWT
Jira / TFS / HP ALM	JUnit / TestNg / Mockito
Scrum	<u>C</u> #
Distributed Systems	LATEX